Finding Aid for the June Wayne Papers LSC.0562
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 5: Four Stones For Kanemitsu, 1969-1974
  - Transcript Aug. 29, 1969 A10 and B-6 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Contains two sound reels (5 inch), 1/4 inch (1 7/8 IPS and 3 3/4 IPS) polyester tape in boxes labeled "Litho-Prot- 8/29, B-6 Bob Beban [?], Kentucky Derby 5/4/64, KBIG Hollywood 28, Rita Montgomery" and Litho-10 8/29 A-10 Serge & Mike refer keystone proof cue track (camera roll 41) Monologue Mike referring to new colors"; also includes transcript for B-6.
  - The 49th Academy Awards Best Documentary 1973, 1969, 1970, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Contains two sound reels (5 inch) 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) polyester tape, one without box with label on reel that reads "[Terry] Sanders [...?] Kanemitsu for the first time", and one with box labeled "Litho #18 Mike Kanemitsu at home - Apt. Wild - Kids, baby feeding, 1969 September 24"; one 1/2 inch color video film [format not identified] reel (5 inch) with box labeled "46th Academy Awards Best Documentary 1973" (held 1974 April 2); also includes transcript, "'Homage to a Lithograph' a film by Terry Sanders" (1970 April 24-25) and Wayne's notes re Movieola showing at Sanders (1970 April 6 or 13.)
  - Transcript Aug. 30, 1969 A-13 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 13, 8/30/69 A13", "Serge [Lozingot] & Mike [Kanemitsu] re proofs 8/30, Press FX, Serge & Gene [Sturman] end of run"; also includes transcription of "A- 13 Aug. 30th"
  - Transcript Sept 4, 1969 A-15 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 15, 9/14, A-15", "Lithography 15, Mike [Kanemitsu] re final print, Serge [Lozingot] & Gene [Sturman] re black print Cam R 51, Serge & Gene last print (cue trk), Last print FX, Serge checking prints"; also includes transcription [TS = Terry Sanders; MK = Mike Kanemitsu; GS = Gene Sturman.]
  - Transcript Sept 3, 4, 1969 A-14 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 14, 9/2,3,4, A-14", "Lithography 14. Gene [Sturman] & Serge [Lozingot] re red prints, Gene re last print, Gene, Serge, Mike Kanemitsu re final print, 1969 September 2, 3, 4; also includes transcription.
  - Transcript Sept 5, 1969 A-17 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 17 - 9/15, A-17" 1969 September 5, and "Monologue, Mike [Kanemitsu]; Serge [Lozingot] & Mike re black and white print; Wild FX rolling ink and stone printing, gumming stone, washing of gum, sponging inking roller with spatula; Cam roll 53 (cue trk); Serge & Mike re print & cancellation; Printing cycle without inking of [illeg]; Close in printer roller; Last print (cue trk), Com. Roll 54; Cancellation (cue trk); also includes transcription, "LITHO A 17/9-5-69."
  - Transcript Sept 26, 1969 A-19 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho T-19, A-19, 1969 September 26", "Tamarind T-19", and "Signing Prints in Curating Room"; also includes transcription.
  - Tape Transcript Aug 26, 1969 A-6 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 6, A-6, 1969 August 26", "Monologue Mike evaluates stone"; also includes transcript.
  - Transcript Aug. 25, 1969 A-5 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Transcript Aug. 27, 28, 1969 A-7 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 5, A-6, 1969 August 25", "Monologue Gene referring to powder and rosing"; also includes transcript.
  - Transcript Aug. 28 & 29 1969 A-8 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 8, A-8, 1969 August 28", "Tape 8: Serge [Lozingot] and Gene [Sturman] refer to third stone; song by Gene; Serge and Mike [Kanemitsu] refer to 2nd stone; Monologue Mike refer 1st lithograph Monologue Serge refer black on 3rd stone; Serge, Mike, Gene refer black on 3rd stone; Mike refer 3rd color and registration; Mike Serge referring proofing; Mike, Gene, Serge refer colors"; also includes transcript.
  - Transcript Aug. 29, 1969 A-9 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 9, A-9, 1969 August 29", and "Mike [Kanemitsu] and Serge [Lozingot] re 3rd proof; Monologue Mike re artists; Mike and Serge re 3rd proof"; also includes transcription.
  - Transcript Aug. 30, 1969 A-12 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 12, A-12, 1969 August 30", and "Serge [Lozingot] and Mike [Kanemitsu] re proofs, cue trks & FX; also includes transcription.
  - Transcript Aug. 29-30, 1969 A-11 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Contains one sound tape reel (5 inch), 1/4 inch (3 3/4 IPS) Acetate tape in box labeled "Litho 11, A-11, 1969 August 29", and "Mike [Kanemitsu] and Serge [Lozingot] re new colors; Monologue Gene [Sturman]; Serge & Mike re proofs; Serge mixing colors (FX); Printing (FX)"; also includes transcription.
- Series 6: June Wayne's Events, 1976-1997
  This series is organized into five subseries: Conference, Exhibits, Panel, Trip, and Datebooks.
  This series includes correspondence and supportive documents regarding Wayne's speaking engagements, participation in conferences, exhibitions of her work, and personal and professional appointments.
  - Subseries 1: Conference, 1994-1999
    This subseries includes correspondence regarding Wayne's participation in various conferences on graphic arts and women's issues. Also includes conference schedules, brochures, and related ephemera.
    - Antelope Valley. Mar 6 '98, 1998, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      Correspondents include: Elaine D. Crump (Antelope Valley College, Lancaster, CA) re Wayne being keynote speaker for the Women's Conference, "Women Create!" at Antelope Valley College (1999 March 6.)
    - Athens Ohio March So. Graphics Conference 1998, 1997, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Correspondents include: Anita Jung (Assistant Professor of Art, School of Art, Ohio University, Athens, OH) re Wayne's participation in 26th Annual Southern Graphics Council Conference, "A Celebration of the Print, 200th Anniversary of Lithography" (Ohio University, Athens, OH, 1998 March 25-28); also includes: conference flyer, brochure, and program; issue of newsletter, "Graphic Impressions" about the conference; brief Wayne biography.
    - CAA Panel 2009, 2008 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Cincinnati 1998 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      Correspondents include: Don Kelley (College of Design, Architecture, Art and Planning, Cincinnati, OH) and April Foster (Art Academy of Cincinnati) re Wayne being keynote speaker at Third Biennial Mid America Print Council Conference, "Pressing Issues" (1998 October 7-11, University of Cincinnati, Cincinnati, OH); also includes conference programs, schedules, and reference materials.
    - Cincinnati Ohio 200th Anniv. Jung, Kelly Keynote Oct. 98., 1997, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      Correspondents include: Anita Jung (College of Fine Arts, Ohio University, Athens, OH) re 26th Annual Southern Graphics Council Conference, "A Celebration of the Print, 200th Anniversary of Lithography" (Ohio University, Athens, OH, 1998 March 25-28); Don Kelley (School of Art, College of Design, Architecture, Art, and Planning, Cincinnati, OH) re Wayne being the keynote speaker for the Third Biennial Mid America Print Council Conference, "Pressing Issues" (University of Cincinnati, Cincinnati, OH, 1998 October 7-11); April Foster re materials needed from Wayne for "Pressing Issues" conference; Donna Burns (Director, Community Outreach Education, Pressing Issues Conference Facilitation) and Cindy Curtis re Wayne's travel arrangements for attending the "Pressing Issues" conference; also includes announcement for call for proposals, conference schedule, issue of "MAPC", the journal of the Mid America Print Council (Fall/Winter 1997), and brochure for "Image & Text II Symposium" (Stephen F. Austin State University, Nacogdoches, TX, 1998 November 4-7.)
    - Knoxville Southern Graphics Conference March '95, 1994, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Correspondents include: Beauvais Lyons (President, Southern Graphics Council) re Wayne receiving 1995 Southern Graphics Council Printmaker Emeritus Award, exhibition of Wayne's work entitled, "One Printmaker to Another", and attending 23rd Annual SGC conference, "Beyond Labels" at University of Tennessee, Knoxville, TN (1995 March 15-18); Stephen Wicks (Curator, Knoxville Museum of Art, Knoxville, TN) re slides of Wayne's work; Boyd Saunders (Printmaker Emeritus Awards coordinator and Professor of Art, University of South Carolina, Columbia, SC) re biographical information about Wayne; also includes checklist of prints for Wayne's exhibition, copy of SGC Newsletter (Summer 1994), "Beyond Labels" conference programs, schedules, and reference materials.
    - New York City Trip, February 2000 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia Print Collaboration -- James, Theresa, 2005 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Southern Graphic Council -- Lyons, Beauvais, 1996-2002 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Univ. Ohio - Cincinnati, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      Correspondents include: April Foster (Art Academy of Cincinnati, Cincinnati, OH) re thank you for Wayne's participation in Mid America Print Council Conference "Pressing Issues" and exhibition of "The Dorothy Series" at the Skirball Museum (Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion, Cincinnati, OH); Donna Burns (Director, Community Outreach Education, Pressing Issues Conference Facilitation) re reimbursement of Wayne's expenses.
    - Women's Council for Art, 2008-2011 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Women's Council for Art -- 1999 Conference, 1988-2007 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Exhibits, 1981-1991
    - Bunkamura Exhibit, 1991, 1992, 1993, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Correspondents include: Takaoki Suzuki (General Manager, Tokyu Bunkamura) re exhibition of Wayne's work; also includes eight 4.5 x 6.5 inch color photographs of the gallery space and brochure, and Bunkamura Gallery layout plans (1991 November 26.)
    - Sylmar Show March 97, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      Correspondents include: John Cantley (Director, Century Gallery, Los Angeles Mission College, Los Angeles, CA) re inclusion of Wayne's work in exhibition, "Quarks to Quasars" to be held 1997 April 13-May 9; Jay Belloli (Armory Center for The Arts, Pasadena, CA) re release of Wayne's "Stellar Winds" and "Silent Wind" to Merrilyn Duzy (Curator, Century Gallery.)
    - Binghampton Lynn Gamwell, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      Correspondents include: Lynn Gamwell (Director, University Art Museum, Binghamton University, Binghamton, NY) re showing prints from Wayne's exhibition at the Neuberger Museum of Art (State University of New York, Purchase, NY) at the New York Academy of Sciences; also includes sample brochures.
    - Feb/Armory Show '97 Weisberg., 1996, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      Correspondents include: Linda Centell (Curator, The Armory Center for the Arts, Pasadena, CA) and Jay Belloli (Director of Gallery Programs) re inclusion of Wayne's work in exhibition, "Changing Media: Books and Prints" (1997 February 1-April 6); also includes loan agreement form, list of Wayne's works loaned for the exhibition, and Wayne biography (as of 1996 September.)
    - Exhibition Knoxville 1995 & others, 1950-1958, 1970-1983, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      Includes list of Wayne's solo exhibitions (1935-1992); exhibition checklists for Art Institute of Chicago (1952 April 25-May 25); "Tapestries and Lithographs by June Wayne" (Cypress College, Cypress, CA, 1977 March 14-April 1); "The Messenger Painting and Forty Drawings and Prints" (de Young Museum of Art, San Francisco, CA, 1956); "One Printmaker to Another" (Knoxville Art Museum, Knoxville, TN, 1995); "Forty Lithographs by June Wayne" (Museum of Art, University of Iowa, Iowa City, IA, 1970 January 19-February 28); "Paintings and Lithographs by June Wayne" (La Jolla Museum of Contemporary Art, La Jolla, CA, 1954 February 9); "June Wayne's Lithographs" (Palm Springs Desert Museum, 1977 December 2-1978 January 8); "Lithographies et Tapisseries de June Wayne" (Rubicon Gallery, Los Altos, CA, 1977); "Paintings by June Wayne" (San Francisco Museum of Art, 1950 August 1-27); "Shortcuts, Feathers, Winds" (San Jose Institute of Contemporary Art, 1983); Santa Barbara Museum of Art (1953 January 19-February 8 and 1958 September); Van Doren Gallery (San Francisco, CA, 1974 March-April and 1976 April-May); also includes letter from Linda Tyler (Gallery Director, Tamarind Institute, University of New Mexico, Albuquerque, NM) to Wayne re inclusion of Wayne's print, "Nos Portraits en 2060" in traveling exhibition, "Tamarind: Into the Nineties," initiated by the Weatherspoon Art Gallery, University of North Carolina at Greensboro.
    - Exhibition Knoxville 1995 & others, 1979, 1980, 1983-1986, 1989, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      Includes exhibition checklists for "My Palomar and Beyond" (Associated American Artists Gallery, New York, NY, 1985 November); "50 Works in 3 Media: June Wayne" (Arizona State University Gallery, Tempe, AZ, 1979); "Cognitos" (Armstrong Gallery, New York, NY); Selections from "The Djuna Set" (Benton Gallery, East Hampton, NY, 1989 June); "Lithographs by June Wayne: A Retrospective" (Cincinnati Art Museum, Cincinnati, OH, 1969); "My Palomar and Beyond" (Macalester College Art Galleries, St. Paul, MN, 1986 October 17-November 12); "June Wayne: Before Cosmos" (Occidental College, Los Angeles, CA, 1980 November 3-December 12); Selections from "The Djuna Set" (Montgomery Gallery, Pomona College, Claremont, CA, 1992 March); "My Palomar, Stellar Winds, Solar Flares: Lithographs by June Wayne" (The Print Club, Philadelphia, PA, 1985); "June Wayne Before Tamarind" (Tobey C. Moss Gallery, Los Angeles, CA, 1983 June 27); "June Wayne" (Tobey C. Moss Gallery, 1984 December); consignment of Wayne's "At Last a Thousand II" to Tobey C. Moss Gallery (1986 January 24.)
    - Claremont Show 3/92, 1991, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      Correspondents include: Marjorie "Cricket" L. Harth (Director, Montgomery Gallery, Pomona College, Claremont, CA) and Kay Koeninger re exhibition of Wayne's work; also includes gallery layouts, loan forms, price lists, Pomona College Associates reception announcement and exhibition calendar (1991/92.)
    - Mar 19 '98- Panel USC/LACMA, 1997, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      Correspondents include: Ruth Weisberg (Dean of Fine Arts, University of Southern California (USC)), Lynn Zelevansky (Associate Curator, Modern and Contemporary Art, Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA), Los Angeles, CA) and Jill Martinez (Curatorial Assistant, LACMA) re Wayne's participation in joint LACMA/USC symposium, "Women Artists of the 1960s," held 1998 March 19 in conjunction with the exhibition, "Love Forever: Yayoi Kusama, 1958 to 1968"; also includes copy of professional services contract and Wayne biography; page from the Los Angeles Times with article, "Abstraction as Illusion" (1998 March 11) on Yayoi Kusama exhibition at LACMA.
    - Southern Graphics P. Soc. 20th Anniversary, 1995, 1996, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      Correspondents include: Beauvais Lyons (Department of Art, University of Tennessee, Knoxville, TN) re invitation for Wayne's participation in exchange portfolio, "Drawn to Stone," celebrating the bicentennial of lithography; Carmon Colangelo (Chair, Division of Art, South Graphics Council) re invitation for Wayne's participation in 24th annual conference at West Virginia University from 1996 March 6-10; also includes issue of Southern Graphics Council newsletter, "Graphic Impressions" (Fall 1996.)
    - Fresno Art Center & Museum 1985 - 1987, 1986, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      Correspondents include: Bette Chase (Education Coordinator, Fresno Arts Center and Museum, Fresno, CA) re donation of "The Art of June Wayne" and Wayne's lecture at Fresno Museum; Robert Barrett (Executive Director) re exhibition of Wayne's prints, painting and tapestries, held 1988 May 3- August 4, and visit to Wayne's studio on Los Angeles Art Tour, 1987 January 31-February 1; Anita Shanahan and Jane Cleave re visit to Wayne's studio; Wayne's participation as honored guest of Endowment Society luncheon, 1987 May 13; Virginia Farquhar re gift of Wayne's print, "Silent Wind" from Fresno board of trustees and Council of 100; Nancy Barg re lunch with Wayne; Barrett to Lloyd Rigler (Ledler Foundation and Adolph's Foundation, Burbank, CA) re request for support for production of exhibition catalogue; Barrett re Wayne's attendance at Fresno Arts Center and Museum Trustees' Retreat (1987 September 25 & 26); also includes Wayne biography (as of 1987 October); Wayne to Barrett re contacting Lannon Foundation re grant money; Kenneth C. Pascal (Chair, University Lecture Series, California State University, Fresno) re Wayne lecture for Spring 1988 program; Barrett to Arlene Raven re writing essay about Wayne's paintings for Fresno exhibition catalogue; David Salanitro (Designer of Exhibitions, Fresno Arts Center and Museum) re diagram of Arts Center exhibition space; also includes "Budget for June Wayne Exhibition" and issue of Fresno Arts Center and Museum newsletter, "Preview" (Winter 1987.)
    - Fresno Art Center & Museum 1985 - 1987, 1983, 1985, 1986, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      Correspondents include: Kjersti Reed (Curator of Education, Fresno Arts Center and Museum, Fresno, CA) and Bette Chase (Education Coordinator) re Wayne's participation in lecture series; Joyce B. Aiken (Guest Curator) re Women's Year Program and Wayne's participation in exhibition, "In the Advent of Change" (1986 October 12-December 28) at Fresno Arts Center and Museum; thank you letters from Wayne to Joyce Aiken, Virginia Farquar, Jane Cleaves, and Bette Chase; also includes description of Women's Year Program exhibitions, brief list of exhibition details; loan agreement form (1986 August 11); list of artists in exhibition; and exhibition catalogue, "Robert Cremean's Narcissus Pentology 1971-1982" (Fresno Arts Center, 1983 March 15-April 28); page from Artweek magazine with article by Leigh Ann Clifton, "Fixed for Life: Fresno Art Museum strikes a deal" (1992 May 21.)
    - Fresno Art Center & Museum 1988-, 1987-1990, 1993-1997 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Correspondents include: Patti Handley (artist) re exhibition and poster of Wayne's work; Robert Bennett re price list for Wayne's tapestries and print suites, "My Palomar", "Solar Flares", and "Stellar Winds"; David Salanitro (Designer of Exhibitions, Fresno Arts Center and Museum) re slides of installation; Samuel M. Gerupper (Assistant Director, MacArthur Fellows Program) to Robert Barrett (Director/Chief Curator, Fresno Arts Center) re nomination of Wayne for fellowship; Jane Cleave re visit to Wayne's studio; Barrett re video footage from television interview; Wayne's speech given at College Art Association (CAA) conference in 1990; Mary Anne Graham-Dolorian (Registrar) re Wayne's donation of three prints, "Dorothy the Last Day", "Dead Center II" and "Tenth Memory" to the Fresno Art Museum (1990 July 3); Barrett re Wayne's trips to Australia and Japan; Anita Shanahan (Trustee, Fresno Art Museum) re gala celebration for Robert Barrett on his tenth anniversary as director; Wayne to the California Arts Council re Fresno Art Museum and their Award for Distinguished Service to Wayne; Barrett re schedule for Wayne's visit and lecture (1994 September 16- 18); Jacqueline Pilar (Associate Curator) and Jothan McGaughey (Registrar) re Wayne's participation in exhibition, "Fifteen Profiles: Distinguished California Modernists"; Suzanne Sloan Lewis (Selection Committee, Council of 100, Fresno Art Museum) re Wayne's suggestions for future honorees of the Annual Distinguished Woman's Artist's Award and exhibition.
    - Fresno Art Center & Museum 1988- (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Includes: invitation to buffet dinner honoring June Wayne; layout of Fresno Art Museum's exhibition space; transcription of interview of Wayne by Robert Barrett (Director/Chief Curator, Fresno Arts Center); loan agreement for "The Djuna Set" (1988 March 28); correspondents include: Margie Phillips (Procurement Assistant, California State University, Fresno) and M. Susan Vasquez (Program Coordinator) re Wayne giving lecture, "Leonardo and I, Trekking the Galaxies" on 1988 April 26; Barrett re list of designations of Wayne's prints included in exhibition (1988 February 23); Anita Shanahan (Trustee, Fresno Art Museum) re visit to Wayne's studio; Les Estrin (for Lloyd Rigler, The Ledler Foundation, Burbank, CA) to Barrett re grant for funding production of exhibition catalogue; Linda Fasulo (Wayne's assistant) to Barrett re name and address lists for exhibition invitations; Bernard Kester (Acting Dean, University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA)) re essay about Wayne's tapestry work for proposed catalogue; Virginia Varquhar (Chairman, Council of 100) re Wayne's visit and receiving the first Annual Distinguished Woman's Artist's Award and Wayne's donation of 10 prints to the museum; David Salanitro (Designer of Exhibitions) re color samples for exhibition design; Barrett re Wayne's visit to Fresno Art Museum; George Y. Blair (Chair, Acquisitions Committee, Fresno Art Museum) re Wayne's exhibition.
    - Lucas, Judy/ Skirball Cincinnati, OH, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      Correspondents include: Judy Lucas (Curator, Skirball Museum, Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion, Cincinnati, OH) re Wayne speaking at opening of exhibition, "June Wayne: The Dorothy Series."
    - Honolulu Show Sept 98, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      Correspondents include: Beauvais Lyons (Ellen McClung Berry Professor of Art, College of Arts and Science, University of Tennessee, Knoxville, TN) re Wayne's participation in exhibition, "Contents and Context: Lithography After 200 Years," by the Honolulu Printmakers Workshop (Academy Art Center, Honolulu, HI, 1998 October 4-30); also includes exhibition brochure.
    - Laguna Art Museum, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Correspondence with Bolton Colburn (Senior Curator, Laguna Art Museum, Laguna, CA) re provenance of Wayne's print "A Little Nothing", gifted to the museum by Nancy Dustin Wall Moure.
    - SECURITY PACIFIC BANK 1980 - EXHIBITION, 1979, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Includes list of Wayne's works loaned for exhibition at Security Pacific National Bank (Los Angeles, CA) from 1980 January 28-March 30; also includes loan agreement forms and loan return receipts.
    - Miami University 1998-99 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with Edna C. Southard (Curator of Collections, Art Museum, Miami University, Oxford, OH) re exhibition, "Paper and Stone: 19th and 20th Century Lithographs" which includes Wayne's lithograph, "Tenth Memory" (1998 July 28.)
    - UNIVERSITY OF ALABAMA/BIRMINGHAM (A. Tony Johnson, J.W. Schnorrenberg, S. Armstrong, S. Fuller), 1982, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      Correspondents include: Sara Garden Armstrong, Anne H. Arrasmith, Scott Fuller (Birmingham Art Association, Birmingham, AL), John M. Schnorrenberg (Chairman, Department of Art, University of Alabama, Birmingham, AL, and Toni Johnson (Visual Arts Gallery) re Wayne's lecture and exhibition of Wayne's "The Dorothy Series" at the Visual Arts Gallery, University of Alabama (Birmingham, AL) (1982 September 6.)
    - Conejo Valley Art Museum 1983 (Box 44, Folder 6)